[
    {
        "front": "Hajimemashite",
        "back": "Nice to meet you",
        "chapter": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "Watashi",
        "back": "I",
        "chapter": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "Des",
        "back": "is, am, are",
        "chapter": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "Dōzo ",
        "back": "(Spoken while offering something)",
        "chapter": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "Yoroshiku",
        "back": "Favors (Greetings)",
        "chapter": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "Indo",
        "back": "India",
        "chapter": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "Jin",
        "back": "(Suffix for Nationality)",
        "chapter": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "Indojin",
        "back": "Indian",
        "chapter": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "Nihonjin",
        "back": "Japanese",
        "chapter": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "Chūgokujin",
        "back": "Chinese",
        "chapter": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "Amerikajin",
        "back": "American",
        "chapter": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "Gakusei",
        "back": "Student",
        "chapter": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "Sensei",
        "back": "Teacher, Professor",
        "chapter": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "Kirei",
        "back": "Beautiful",
        "chapter": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "Takai",
        "back": "Expensive",
        "chapter": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "Hiroi",
        "back": "Wide",
        "chapter": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "Tomodachi",
        "back": "Friend",
        "chapter": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "Shain / Kaishain",
        "back": "Employee / Company Employee",
        "chapter": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "hai",
        "back": "Yes",
        "chapter": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "iie",
        "back": "No",
        "chapter": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "San",
        "back": "(Honorifics; “honorable Mr/Ms.”)",
        "chapter": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "Chan",
        "back": "(Honorific for Kids and…)",
        "chapter": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "India ",
        "back": "Indo",
        "chapter": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "Japan",
        "back": "Nihon",
        "chapter": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "America",
        "back": "Amerika",
        "chapter": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "China",
        "back": "Chūgoku",
        "chapter": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "Korea",
        "back": "Kankoku",
        "chapter": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "France",
        "back": "Furansu",
        "chapter": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "Germany",
        "back": "Doitsu",
        "chapter": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "Italy",
        "back": "Itaria",
        "chapter": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "Russia",
        "back": "Roshia",
        "chapter": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "Indian",
        "back": "Indojin",
        "chapter": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "Japanese (citizen)",
        "back": "Nihonjin",
        "chapter": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "American",
        "back": "Amerikajin",
        "chapter": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "Chinese (citizen)",
        "back": "Chūgokujin",
        "chapter": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "Korean (citizen)",
        "back": "Kankokujin",
        "chapter": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "French (citizen)",
        "back": "Furansujin",
        "chapter": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "German (citizen)",
        "back": "Doitsujin",
        "chapter": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "Italian (citizen)",
        "back": "Itariajin",
        "chapter": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "Russian (citizen)",
        "back": "Roshiajin",
        "chapter": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "Hindi",
        "back": "Hindigo",
        "chapter": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "Japanese (language)",
        "back": "Nihongo",
        "chapter": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "English",
        "back": "Eigo",
        "chapter": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "Chinese (language)",
        "back": "Chūgokugo",
        "chapter": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "Korean (language)",
        "back": "Kankokugo",
        "chapter": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "French (language)",
        "back": "Furansugo",
        "chapter": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "German (language)",
        "back": "Doitsugo",
        "chapter": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "Italian (language)",
        "back": "Itariago",
        "chapter": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "Russian (citizen)",
        "back": "Roshiago",
        "chapter": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "Minna San",
        "back": "everyone, all of you",
        "chapter": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "Genki",
        "back": "health, energy, vigor",
        "chapter": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "Anata",
        "back": "You",
        "chapter": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "Injinia",
        "back": "Engineer",
        "chapter": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "Isha",
        "back": "Doctor",
        "chapter": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "Ano kata",
        "back": "That Person",
        "chapter": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "Donata",
        "back": "Who",
        "chapter": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "Sakura",
        "back": "Name of a University",
        "chapter": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "Daigaku",
        "back": "University",
        "chapter": 1
    }
]